It's not that cold and…
What's going on?
A ghost?
Who turned them off?
A SUDDEN BLACKOUT?
10 MINUTES EARLIER
It's so hot. I can't stay here.
Gosh, it's too hot.
KIAN RUNS AWAY FROM THE HEAT
It's already 10:00 p.m.?
I should turn a light off.
THE SWITCHES ARE 3.5 M HIGH
KITCHEN
LIVING ROOM
TARGET
THE LIVING ROOM LIGHT SWITCH
Darn it!
Was it this hard to turn them off?
Geez, every single thing.
Nothing's easy to do.
What on earth am I doing?
This is so inconvenient!
Focus.
What? I turned them all off.
ALL LIGHTS ARE TURNED OFF NOW
This wasn't what I wanted.
I need to turn one on.
No, it's not a blackout.
- I think Boss turned it off.
- Really?
- They're all off.
- I know.
- One will be on soon.
- Let's wait.
BUT HE'S NOT TURNING THEM BACK ON?
FUMBLING WITH SOMETHING IN THE DARK
HE INVENTED A TOOL?
There we go.
Okay.
If you want beer, come here.
Okay!
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Goodness.
That's nice.
This is so nice.
I was so thirsty.
You're not puffy at all now.
The sauna was so nice.
I feel less tired today.
BEFORE, AFTER
I feel so good now.
The puffiness is all gone.
- The dinner went well too.
- Right.
Okay, cheers.
Cheers.
Very nice.
- Cheers.
This is so nice.
I'll turn the lights off.
You can go to bed
or drink and talk more if you want.
Are you okay, Zuha?
- Yes.
- You're lasting a long time.
Of course. We're in it together.
By the way, how are you finding it here?
It's… It's difficult
because I haven't done this before.
Meeting strangers like this
is something I haven't done much before.
Isn't it tough?
But it's fun.
Plus, you're trying something new here.
That's not easy.
I mean, it's not just you,
it's hard for everyone.
It's also fun, isn't it?
- It is. I'm about to cry.
- She's crying.
It's tough.
CHOKING UP
It's also fun, right?
- It's fun. It is, but…
- Yeah.
It's tough.
She says it's tough.
What do you find tough, Zuha?
Well, it's quite hard for me
to join conversations.
Conversations? I thought so.
I think it's because of the language.
Her Korean's good.
It is, but I think she's still cautious.
I mean, her Korean's good,
but I think her personality is…
- Right.
- Introverted.
Yeah, her Korean's real good though.
Up until the third day,
it felt so awkward.
It was my first time
meeting strangers like that,
so it felt so new to me.
- You feel awkward?
- A bit.
- Like that? Oh, I see.
- Yes.
I get it now.
Hey, Zuha.
- Yes?
- What are you doing?
I'm bored.
Come on over.
Can I?
Why didn't you come?
I was still not sure
what kind of role I should play
at that time,
so when they brought that up,
I think that's why I teared up.
So it's tougher.
But you don't show it.
So you should open yourself up more.
People are used to seeing me around.
But people rarely have
the chance to meet you.
- Right?
- It's rare.
Yeah, so you should do
whatever you feel like doing.
Since you're the youngest,
I'm sure it's not easy to approach others.
But don't explain everything to her.
- Why not?
- Just let her do what she wants to do.
If you explain, she can't do it.
PUZZLED
HE WANTED TO CONSOLE HER, BUT…
Just ignore them.
GONE OFF THE PATH NOW
But that's not easy for someone like her.
This show's for you!
HIS RAISED VOICE
MAKES HER CRY EVEN MORE
Why are you making her cry?
No, no.
Hey.
I…
I cried too, you know.
When did you cry?
I cried too during Season 1.
But it is tough though.
During the day, I was also…
I didn't know what to do today either.
Tomorrow,
let's talk it over, Zuha.
But do I give you a hard time…
No, let's talk tomorrow.
No.
I was worried
I might be giving you a hard time.
No, definitely not.
To me, you are…
I'm very grateful.
Don't feel that way.
You have nothing to be sorry about.
We're grateful that you joined us.
I mean it.
- Sorry.
- Did you fart?
I'm sorry. I let out a little gas.
So that's what the sound was.
- I wondered what it was.
- It won't smell though.
- Damn it.
- I thought only I heard it.
I was trying hard to hold it in,
but a little came out.
I'M SORRY
Let's go to bed now.
Are you okay?
You'll get puffy eyes.
They're so puffy already.
It's crazy.
I hope it's not bad tomorrow.
Thank you.
It's all right.
SOFA, FRIDGE
Good night.
WINDOWSILL
TV CABINET
RAMYEON BOXES
BOSS SLEEPS IN THE KARAOKE ROOM
HANGERS
LIVING ROOM
I hope it snows a bunch.
2:00 A.M.
DAY 4
KIAN'S B&B
It's so white.
IT'S WHITE EVERYWHERE
7:00 A.M.
It's beautiful.
KIAN'S B&B
There's a bench.
Come quickly to help me, Lord.
MORNING PRAYERS AT A SNOWY KIAN'S B&B
JUN-HO GETS UP
ZUHA GETS UP
He's awake.
GI-PYO'S UP
Wake up.
GROANING
THE BOSS GETS UP
MORNING EXERCISE
MORNING EXERCISE ENDS
Jin-an, do you need sunscreen?
No, we'll get wet anyway when we surf.
I'll bring one.
Thank you.
- And you're going with them, Jun-ho?
- Yes.
After surfing,
we'll go skiing and snowboarding.
Are you leaving now?
Yeah. Today's your last day.
Yeah, last day.
Yes.
- See you again.
- See you.
SAYING GOODBYE TO THOSE CHECKING OUT TODAY
Goodbye, Father. I'll miss you.
My brother.
We'll get going.
- See you later.
- Bye.
- See you.
Be safe.
9:30 A.M.
LUGE TEAM & JUN-HO GO OUT
Checkout is at 11:00 a.m.
Well, let's say goodbye to them.
All right.
Does Zuha seem okay?
WORRIED
Did it bother you?
It's bothering you, isn't it?
Well, it seemed like
it's been really tough for her.
BOSS IS WORRIED ABOUT ZUHA
I feel bad.
What do I do?
SHE'S WORRIED TOO
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I think we should have a chat later
with them like yesterday.
Yes, sounds good. Let's do it.
MEANWHILE, THE GUESTS GET READY
TO CHECK OUT
It's a T-shirt,
so I should fold it like one.
Once we go back home,
we have to return to work.
Yeah, I don't even want to think about it.
How did we even bring all this stuff here?
This is so much.
How can we pack all of this up?
We have to.
WE HAVE TO PACK TO GO HOME
There we go.
- It's already 10:30 a.m.
- Right.
We're leaving soon.
Before you check out and leave,
if there's an employee you'd like to
talk to for the last time…
- It's time.
- Yes.
CHECKOUT TALK
WITH CHOSEN STAFF
We'll humbly accept the results.
SHUFFLES BACK
What?
This wasn't what we planned to do.
Four-on-four.
This isn't some reality dating show.
IN FORMATION
- Is this The Mate?
- This feels strange.
Should we turn around? What should we do?
Do you want to stand behind us?
Yeah, let's do that.
Then, could you go back and spread out…
- Okay.
- Spread out?
- All right.
Do we turn around?
Let's try it.
Should we close our eyes?
4-ON-4
CUPID'S ARROWS
CHOOSE YOUR STAFF MEMBER!
I'll go last.
- We won't look.
- We won't.
Let's go.
Here we go.
You can do it all at once.
WHO WILL THE GUESTS CHOOSE?
Are you done?
- Okay.
- We'll turn around now.
One, two, three.
AND THE RESULT?
Almost everyone.
Is this for real?
I got one.
SNEHAL CHOSE YEON-KOUNG
One, two, three.
NO ONE PICKED KIAN YESTERDAY
SEUL, SANG-CHEON, AND SMITA CHOSE KIAN
I'm so touched.
Thank you.
ZUHA GOT 0 VOTES
JUN-HO GOT 0 VOTES
Zuha.
Where should we start cleaning?
- Let's work hard.
- Right.
- Goodness.
- We're not sad at all.
I really wanted to pick you, but…
We're not sad at all.
It's okay. We're not sad.
NOT SAD WITH A STICKY ROLLER
Jun-ho. Clean hard, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
NOT SAD WHILE EMPTYING A BIN
Boss will do it outside.
So let's do it here.
Go chat with Boss.
YEON-KOUNG & SNEHAL
How was it here?
It was so fun.
I've never been this happy
throughout a stay in my life.
Thank you.
No, we should thank you.
I'm so grateful you worked so hard for us.
But you know, you two are so cheerful
and get along so well with other people.
It made me think.
I've spent a lot of time abroad too.
MORE THAN 10 YEARS OVERSEAS
So I know well how difficult it can be
to live abroad as a foreigner.
I know how hard it can be for you.
Please don't do that.
No, I mean it.
Since I know how hard it can be,
I find it very admirable.
- Why am I suddenly crying?
- Goodness.
TEARING UP AFTER RELATING
I'll go get some tissues.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
HUGE TOILET PAPER
Why are you crying?
Come here.
I'm young and in my twenties now,
but I think I should live
as if I were in my thirties
to make it easier on myself later on.
With that in mind,
I want to enjoy my life.
And I've always thought this.
If I work hard for a long time,
I can be successful in anything.
So, I just believe and keep going,
even if there's no path.
Sometimes, that kind of mindset
is important.
"Just keep going, and it'll all work out."
It'll all build up
and pay off in the future.
Why am I crying?
I'm not usually like this.
It's okay.
- I'm sad that I'm leaving.
- I totally get it.
It's a shame.
Right, it is.
- Smita?
- That's right.
Smita, right?
Was it okay? Did you like it?
KIAN
CHAE-SEUL, SANG-CHEON, SMITA
I haven't had many chances
to get close to Korean people.
And I got to do a lot of that here,
so I really loved that.
I'm glad.
I'm sad that I have to leave.
- So…
- Honestly?
Of course.
Three days went by so fast.
- Yes, it was so short.
- Tell me about it.
On the other hand, it must be hard for you
to welcome and let people go.
Because you get close.
- Me?
- Yes.
When I talk with you, Father,
it makes me feel at peace.
PEACE OF MIND
- Seriously.
- Really?
I don't know why I feel like that.
- But, Kian--
- I'm put at ease.
That's why I'm grateful
to you too, Sam-cheon.
- "Sam-cheon"?
- Thank you for coming here.
You're such a bitch.
"Bitch"?
Such a bitch.
I'm not a bitch.
- I'm bit, or ray of light.
- Right, bit.
- Right, bit!
- Bit, not bitch.
IT'S MY BAD
"Bit"? "Bitch"?
Oh, "bitch"!
HE GETS IT NOW
"You're such a bitch"!
You were all bright like light,
but it's off now.
What do you mean? The light's off?
It's off now?
My light is off now?
- You can feel that?
- Yes.
- Do I look dark?
- Very dark.
SHOCKED
You're always stressed out.
You know those gloomy clouds?
I can see them over you.
A DARK BOSS
Where did your old self go?
I've been worried this entire time.
First off, I planned
and built a fun house,
but I worry someone might get hurt
because of the design.
Well, there's nothing I can do
about that now, but it worries me.
You came here to have fun,
but I wasn't sure
if you found it fun here.
I've been worried about that too.
And safety?
And the most important thing is
for guests to have fun here.
It's so hard.
THAT'S WHY IT'S HARD
To tell you the truth,
I was the biggest problem.
I was so clumsy. I felt so lost.
Be careful there.
"Are they enjoying it?"
Since I was so worried,
I couldn't have proper talks with guests.
WHILE EVERYONE'S HAVING FUN
Today…
KIAN WAS DEEP IN THOUGHT ALONE
I was hesitant.
I think I was the clumsiest one.
So when Smita said
that I was so dark,
I was totally stunned.
Kian, don't worry about that.
You must have fun
so everyone else can truly have fun.
The solution is for you to have fun here.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Well, I have a lot to worry about.
I have a lot on my…
But seriously, thank you for saying that.
It was good advice.
Be cheerful?
- Yes.
- Got it.
It's really valuable advice.
It helped a lot.
I don't know if it'll work,
but when the moment comes,
and if I approach the guests first,
then I believe it'll be better.
- You should go. It's 11:00 a.m.
- Right.
- Thank you for everything, Mr. Kian.
- Thank you.
How did the talks go?
Smita said I was darkness.
Darkness?
No, not darkness.
It's not like that.
I was so hurt.
No, I'm joking.
I know what you meant.
FINALLY, WRITING IN THE VISITORS' LOG
MAY PEACE BE WITH THIS HOUSE
AND EVERYONE STAYING IN IT
PRIEST
MIN SANG-CHEON
THANK YOU FOR BEING SPECIAL PEOPLE
IN MY LIFE THAT I'LL REMEMBER
SPATIAL DESIGNER
CHAE SEUL
Wait… You two are writing a lot.
"Kian and Kazuha,
please don't be so stressed out."
OLDER TWIN
SMITA
"Jun-ho, thanks for the seaweed soup."
That's a big heart around my name.
I HAD SO MUCH FUN THESE THREE DAYS
YOUNGER TWIN
SNEHAL
- We should leave so you can…
- Yes.
CHECKOUT TIME
11:00 A.M.
It's been fun.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
We will. Thank you.
- Be careful of snow.
- Bye!
Good luck, Mr. Kian!
- Okay, good luck!
- Good luck!
It's been a great time.
I love you, Jun-ho!
- Good luck! I love you!
- I love you!
I love you!
I love you all!
SNEHAL, SMITA, SANG-CHEON, SEUL
CHECK OUT
We'll really go now.
What? Because it's a shame to leave?
Yes.
For young people like us
going through a lot of growing pains,
it was where we could be innocent
and show our genuine smiles.
KIAN'S B&B IS "GENUINE"
It reminded me of when we'd play
hide-and-seek as kids.
That innocence.
KIAN'S B&B IS "INNOCENCE"
If I think about everything
I experienced in this house,
despite being foreigners,
we were like family.
KIAN'S B&B IS "FAMILY"
So I was so grateful.
There's no guesthouse host
who treats their guests this well.
I'm sure of it.
- Bye. I had a great time.
- Bye, Kian's B&B.
- Seriously, it'll be fond memories.
- I had so much fun.
- It was like a dream, wasn't it?
- It was.
- It really was.
- We made the best memories ever!
We're going home now.
KIAN'S B&B
- Again, it's…
- Yeah.
- Again.
- They're all gone.
- Goodness.
- This very feeling.
- So empty.
- This feeling after they leave.
Another four have gone.
Is all the cleaning finished?
Yes, it is.
I was exempt from cleaning today.
That's a good thing.
- By the way, Jun-ho.
- Yes?
They announced the news yesterday
about us joining the show.
Right.
You're pretty popular.
- Me?
- He's very popular.
- No way.
- I was so surprised.
No, I'm not.
- Gosh, Jun-ho's so popular.
- No, not at all.
So are you all right?
- Me?
- Yeah.
You're so popular on social media,
but not so much here.
JUN-HO HAS RECEIVED A TOTAL 0 VOTES SO FAR
You're in the kitchen all the time.
- I work so hard to clean up there.
- Right.
Why do you think it's cleaner now?
CLEAN KITCHEN THANKS TO JUN-HO
So you believe
you got
zero votes…
- Because…
- Because all you've done is work?
- Right.
- "All you've done."
That's what I believe.
But I don't dwell on that.
- He makes that sounds cool.
- Yeah.
I'll keep working hard
so you can take good care of our guests.
I'll do my best to support you.
VERY DETERMINED
- What?
- He's the best.
12:00 P.M.
Don't you feel hungry?
Should we eat out?
I'd like that.
- I want to eat at a restaurant.
- Yes.
Chinese food.
Then, shall we have Chinese food
and talk a little?
Should we go now?
Let's go. I'm hungry.
Okay.
You look cool.
- What?
- You look cool.
- Really?
- Yes.
You look a bit like a delinquent.
- If I make this face?
- Yes?
Yes, with that expression.
- Feeling comfortable?
- Yes.
Good. Me too.
I'm scared.
ZUHA FEELS VERY COMFORTABLE NOW
- By the way, Boss is so lucky.
- Why?
These two are doing Kian's B&B
as their first variety show.
I'm so grateful.
You're so blessed.
Isn't meeting you the biggest blessing?
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Why are you being like that to me?
I think what he heard keeps bothering him.
Very dark.
Right?
Whenever I made eye contact, I felt bad.
We don't know which one is the real you.
The me from today
and yesterday are both real.
I've become so cautious.
This is the place.
Hello.
YEON-KOUNG SETS THE TABLE
- Thank you.
Yeon-koung's so good at being in a group.
I think you're a master
of group activities.
What did I do?
I mean, it seems like
you were made to be in a group.
It's because I've been in groups a lot.
But you two have also spent
a lot of time in groups,
so you must be used to it too.
- You still live with the other members.
- Right.
LE SSERAFIM members still live together?
Yes.
- A group of two and a group of three.
- Really?
When you quit ballet to become a singer,
what was the hardest part?
- I wasn't good at Korean at first.
- The language?
So it took a while
to get close to the other members.
Right.
But your pronunciation's so good.
- It's like a native speaker.
- It's great.
- Really?
- People wouldn't know you're Japanese.
- You really think so?
- Yeah.
Did you go somewhere
and learn how to give compliments?
"Let's praise each other."
It feels like "Our Boss Has Changed."
- It's here.
- Pardon me.
- It looks so good.
- The portions are huge.
Isn't it so good?
There's a lot of seafood.
I think we're eating much more today
than we have so far.
Because we've been working hard.
Made with flour…
Should I make pizza today?
It's doable.
BOSS IS TODAY'S CHEF
- How?
- Are you going to make the dough?
I can make it in a frying pan.
When I was a kid,
that's how I always did it.
It sounds good.
It's not cliché,
but I've also never heard of it.
Like kimchi pizza.
Kimchi cheese pizza.
Right, kimchi cheese pizza.
- Cheese sounds good.
- That sounds delicious.
Cheese is a must.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
AFTER BUYING PIZZA INGREDIENTS
AT THE MARKET
How about some coffee?
THEY WILL BUY COFFEE TO GO
That was really fun last night.
- What?
- The photo game.
- It was better than I thought.
- It was.
STARING
- It was fun.
- Right?
Did you tint the lenses?
- Yes.
- Why did you do that?
It kind of makes me look
like a fashionista.
To look stylish?
Don't I look stylish?
I thought it was for your eyesight.
What would you know about fashion?
I know a thing or two.
We should ask Kazuha.
- GV?
- GV.
- Very trendy.
GV.
- GV?
- GV.
You don't know, do you?
- GF?
- GV.
Try to guess the meaning.
It's "GV," not "GF."
Like "get fucked"?
That's a curse word.
It doesn't stand for "fuck."
So what does that mean?
- Tell him again.
- What?
Pronounce it accurately.
GV.
DV?
No, it's…
You're cursing at me, aren't you?
- G.
GV.
GV?
GB?
Is it Japanese?
Of course not.
- Your coffee is ready.
- Thank you.
What does it mean?
- "Good vibes."
It stands for that?
- That's the new slang these days.
- Yes.
Did you know what it meant?
- Come on.
- Of course, she knew.
Boss.
You really knew?
Of course, I knew.
Gosh, it's GB.
I told you it's not "GB."
What?
The scenery's pretty GB.
"GV."
- It's GV.
- V.
It means "good."
- Right, good.
- Yeah.
It really has GV.
The clouds make it look so cool.
Right.
It totally has GV.
CAH.
- You're talking about me, aren't you?
- CAH.
- "Clueless as hell."
- What?
Boss is CAH.
SURFING IN YANGYANG
- Is this the popular county of Yangyang?
- The weather's so nice.
So this is the coastal road.
This is a hot spot for surfers.
Winter surfing. Look at the waves.
This is so nice.
Let's go.
JUKDO BEACH
The waves are nice.
AFTER ENJOYING A WINTER BEACH
THEY TRY SURFING
WOBBLING
WOBBLING HERE TOO
I still have a salty taste in my mouth.
My hands are shaking.
The ski resort.
We should go now.
GI-PYO, JIN-AN, YOUNG-HYUN, JUN-HO
YONGPYONG SKI RESORT
It's my first time this year.
I haven't ridden in ages.
I'm nervous.
I want to race.
That's a nice speed.
Gi-pyo's skiing well.
This feels good.
The view today is so…
I can't believe how it changes every day.
It's snowing like rain.
MORNING AT THE SNOWY KIAN'S B&B
It's sleeting.
SLEETING IN THE AFTERNOON
I'll carry it.
GROCERIES
- Thanks.
- You drove.
Thank you. You're the symbol
of being thoughtful.
Very thoughtful.
- The epitome.
- Our boss has changed.
Want me to carry this too?
Hey, come on.
It feels like we're the ones
returning from a trip.
- Right.
These little trips help you recharge.
- I think it's nice.
- It is.
RETURNING AFTER RECHARGING
1:30 P.M.
We should…
Move it up?
Can you do it?
MOVING IT TO THE KITCHEN
Wait, I'll do it.
Hold on. I'll go up first.
ZUHA FROM DOWNSTAIRS
Lift it up.
Hold on.
Lift.
PUTTING IT ON HER HEAD
Hey, you're strong!
- Be careful.
- Does it reach?
VERY CLOSE
Just a bit higher.
ONE MORE PUSH
- Way to go!
- Don't drop it.
If you do, I'll die.
THEY DID IT THANKS TO STRONG ZUHA
Is your head okay?
It's fine. But it's a mess.
SIDE EFFECT OF STRONG ZUHA
It's ruined.
We just need to do laundry.
- Laundry?
- Yes.
If we stomp on them, it won't take long.
4 DAYS WORTH OF LAUNDRY
TOWELS & SAUNA CLOTHES
IN THE SAUNA LAST NIGHT
Should we just use
the jacuzzi to do laundry?
Should we just do it there?
I think it's a good idea. Let's do that.
JACUZZI IS THE LAUNDRY SPOT
But we have to hang them afterwards.
In there?
Dry them in the sauna
and hang some outside.
SAUNA IS THE DRYING ROOM
I'll give it a try.
All right, let's do it together. Okay.
- Laundry?
- Yes.
BOSS IS PLANNING A MURAL
- Sorry?
- Where do we do laundry?
- Upstairs.
- Upstairs?
How do we move it up?
- Up there…
- Yes?
There's a basket the guests used
to bring the food down yesterday.
This one?
Let's use that to move these one by one.
They must've sweat a lot last night.
4 DAYS OF LAUNDRY
I sweat a lot last night.
Right? They're all so wet.
WET
- Zuha, try pulling it up.
- Okay.
This should be doable.
- It's light still enough, right?
- Yes.
Empty it and bring it back down.
Geez, it stinks.
LET'S GO, STRONG ZUHA
You're pretty strong.
EASILY PULLS UP SECOND LOAD
THIRD LOAD FOLLOWS IMMEDIATELY
You're good at this.
LAUNDRY BOX IS EMPTY NOW
Okay. The last one.
Unbelievable, Zuha.
PULLS UP BASKET A LAST TIME
Okay.
THE PILE IS AS BIG AS ZUHA
Everyone, it's all upstairs now.
I got a call.
The phone's ringing.
Hello?
What?
YES, HELLO
JAPANESE GUESTS
What?
It's a Japanese person.
A CHECK-IN CALL IN JAPANESE
I started learning recently.
TODAY
HE PRACTICED JAPANESE
WHENEVER HE HAD THE CHANCE
Where should we go?
Could you tell me the address?
This place is…
THIS PLACE'S…
This…
This place is…
Yes?
This place's…
HE KEEPS REPEATING IT
- What?
- This place…
I'm sorry.
The address?
- Yes.
- Just a moment, please.
Hello?
IT NATURALLY GOES TO ZUHA
I called because I didn't know
where to go.
I'll text you the address soon.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
Okuru. "To send."
BUMMED OUT
The address.
And would it be okay
if we left our luggage there and went out?
He's asking
if they could leave their luggage here.
Now? Is now okay?
Yes, you can come now.
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
We need to send him the address.
Kian, you put it in and send it.
Gosh, we're so international.
- Indian and Japanese guests.
- Right.
Today's Zuha's day.
We can count on Zuha today.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Me?
But I almost spoke Korean on the phone.
"It's finally time."
That's what I thought.
DAEGWALLYEONG, SUHA-RI
WE GOT IT
LET'S GO, TARO
LEAVING FOR KIAN'S B&B
We have to soak them anyway.
Fill it with water.
Put them in and… Geez, the sweat.
LAUNDRY SPOT IS OPEN
Then, for the first step…
Yeah, stomp on them in there.
I guess we're really handwashing them.
STOMPING FIRST
Get them completely soaked.
Okay, let's first stomp on them
It just hit me.
"It just hit me."
INNER THOUGHTS ESCAPE
Hey, this is like a communal laundry spot.
Yes, it is.
IT WAS A JACUZZI YESTERDAY
IT'S USED FOR DIFFERENT PURPOSE TODAY
HANDWASHING WITH SOAP
- I guess we only have one bar of soap.
- Yeah.
We don't have any more right?
Give me the soap. I'll break it in half.
CUTTING BOARD
There we go.
Okay. I cut it into quarters.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
A BAR OF SOAP FOR EACH
WASHING
IN CHARGE OF SOAPING
KIAN, ZUHA, YEON-KOUNG
Geez, the water.
IN CHARGE OF RINSING
JUN-HO
- It's splashing a lot.
- It can't be helped.
Why is there so much laundry?
This is insane.
When you drew this house,
you should've added a washer.
- A washer?
- Yeah.
Why didn't you draw one?
THERE'S NO WASHING MACHINE
IN THIS HUGE ROOM
Gosh, my back.
BIGGEST DRAWBACK
OF THE JACUZZI LAUNDRY SPOT
My back hurts.
STRAIGHTENING
YOU HAVE TO BEND OVER TO DO LAUNDRY
There's so much laundry.
The sauna was full yesterday.
STILL A LOT LEFT
What's this?
Someone's Zara T-shirt is in here.
WHAT T-SHIRT?
A Zara T-shirt.
That's mine.
- What?
- That's mine.
SHE CAN'T BELIEVE HER EARS
Where should I put wet clothes?
Over there.
There's a box.
Put all the laundry in there.
SO HE PUT HIS T-SHIRT IN
Why did you put your clothes in here?
You said it was a laundry box.
Please wash it clean, Yeon-koung.
Why did you put your own clothes in here?
THE BOSS'S IMPURITIES?
Yeon-koung worries about my underwear
and also washes my clothes.
And I see if you've brushed
your teeth before bed.
Yeah, you check that too.
Yes, and I check if you've showered.
OVERWORKED IN MANY WAYS
IT'S BEEN 20 MINUTES
It's snowing outside.
We're living in 2026,
in the era of burgeoning AI,
and we're handwashing laundry.
WITHOUT TAKING A SINGLE BREAK
THEY REMAIN BENT OVER
Boss, are we doing it right?
- We're doing well, right?
- We are.
ABOUT TO HIT THEIR STAMINA WALL
Look at my face right now.
I'm sweating buckets.
This is Kian's B&B.
HIS CLOTHES ARE SOAKED TOO
- Kian's B&B is so nice.
- Right.
This is…
RIGHT THEN, HE FINDS A PAIR OF PANTS
LONG BLACK PANTS?
Let's give it a go.
SAUNA PANTS ARE SHORT AND BROWN
2ND ROUND OF IMPURITIES FOUND FROM BOSS
Whose pants are these?
It's a mess.
Damn it!
CONFIDENT
Well, you told us to put our laundry in.
He's washing
his own sweatshirt so diligently.
Of course, I should.
TAKES CARE OF 3RD ROUND
OF IMPURITIES HIMSELF
Seriously, why did you put
your own laundry in here?
What? I just did what I was told.
I'M SORRY
A BIZARRE LAUNDRY SPOT
- Just look at me now.
- What?
My clothes are all wet.
Just pretend you used the jacuzzi.
Why am I the only one wet?
- What's with you?
- Why only me?
- Yeon-koung, why am I the only one?
- Hey, you punk.
Why am I the only one wet?
You little punk.
Hey, you little punk.
Everyone.
Just imagine how touched they'll be
when they see we handwashed these.
You wring them, damn it.
WRINGING
When you're done, just throw them there.
- Over there.
- Down there?
We'll hang them downstairs.
Throw them there.
WHILE WASHED CLOTHES ARE FLYING AROUND
IT SAYS "KIAN'S B&B"
THIS PLACE IS AMAZING
IT'S DANGEROUS HERE
Hey, I'll carry your suitcase.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
THE SWEET COUPLE IS WALKING OVER
- It's amazing.
- The door is huge!
I don't think I can reach it.
All right.
How do we get in?
What is this?
CAN I REACH THIS?
What?
How do we get in?
Taro, hang on.
What?
ABOUT TO CHECK IN
- They're here.
- Should I open it for them?
- Yeah.
Be careful when you go down.
It's slippery.
Wipe your feet.
Just a moment, please!
ZUHA SETS OUT
Just a moment, please.
He said, "Just a moment, please."
- Hello.
Hello.
Welcome.
- Hello.
ROLLING DOWN
What is this?
I was so surprised.
I got a very special feeling from it.
I thought,
"We've come to a special house."
Could you help me close the door?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
Sure.
- But how?
- How?
- What do we pull?
- This.
What is this?
It's so heavy!
- It's so heavy!
- Do it, Matsu-chan!
THEY'VE CLOSED THE DOOR
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
You two are a couple, right?
Yes.
I guess it's a couple.
What was "Welcome" again?
- What?
- "Irasshaimase."
Irasshaimase.
- Irasshaimase.
- Hello!
- Hello.
WELCOMING THEM FROM UPSTAIRS
Hello.
Can you speak Korean?
- A little.
- I'm Korean.
- You're Korean?
- Yes.
- I thought you were Japanese.
- I thought so too.
You're Japanese?
- Yes, I am.
- He's Japanese.
My name is Kotaro Kunimatsu.
I live in Tokyo,
and I attend Sophia University.
My name is Kim Yoo-min,
and I'm a college student.
We're a couple.
KOREAN-JAPANESE COUPLE
Then, we'll go out right now.
Okay, just leave your luggage here then.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
See you later.
- See you later.
- See you.
You have to pull it down. Try it.
HE TRIES OPENING IT HIMSELF THIS TIME
Be careful.
Hey, his reactions are different.
He's definitely Japanese.
We'll be back.
Bye.
She's beautiful.
- What?
- She's so cute.
She's amazing.
- She is.
- Yeah.
- She's so cute.
THE KOREAN-JAPANESE COUPLE GOES ON A TRIP
A couple as guests.
- A Korean-Japanese couple.
- Yeah.
BACK TO WRINGING
I'm sure it's better
when two people wring them.
How low are you going to go?
Yeon-koung, could you help me
wring this out too?
It's my shirt.
Please help me wring out my shirt.
My shirt…
Thank you.
Yeon-koung, while we're at it,
could you wring out my pants too?
Damn it. For crying out loud.
These too…
I don't think the sauna
has enough space for all these.
You're right.
I'll go start hanging them.
DRYING IN THE SAUNA
SAUNA DRYING ROOM IS OPEN
Goodness. Geez.
SUDDENLY ATTACKED
JUST A MOMENT AGO ON THE 2ND FLOOR
Good job.
Don't your wrists hurt?
YEON-KOUNG'S NO-LOOK THROW
- Goodness. Geez.
- Goodness, Boss.
SHE THREW IT WHEN HE WAS GONE
HE SUDDENLY APPEARS
SURPRISED
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
No way. I'm so sorry, Boss.
Since she played volleyball,
she hit me directly.
I'm sorry, Boss.
IT FEELS GOOD FOR SOME REASON
SHE TRIES TO TIME IT AGAIN
Geez.
It's so dangerous here.
Geez, there's no more space.
- No more?
- What?
NOT ENOUGH SPACE TO DRY THEM
This is bad.
STILL MORE TO DRY
Maybe we can use some ropes…
Right, we have these ropes.
They're perfect.
Yeon-koung, can't we use these?
MAKING A CLOTHESLINE
If we tie these up in there…
If we put them here, will they hold?
Tie it here and…
And tie it somewhere over there.
What about the door handle?
Then, if we tie it here…
That would make three lines.
It's not bad.
EXTRA SPACE SECURED WITH ROPES
Good idea.
- They'll dry really well.
- Right.
Jun-ho.
Look at how much space
his clothes are taking up.
BOSS'S PAIR OF PANTS 1,
PAIR OF PANTS 2, SWEATSHIRT
That's right. Laundry includes
all of our clothes, you know.
Stop looking at my clothes.
How many are there?
- Look at something else.
- How many are there?
I wanted to wash my clothes
while I was here.
FOR THE REMAINING LAUNDRY
A long line?
We can just tie it there.
ONE END ON THE TOP
Okay.
We should tie it up here.
OTHER END BEHIND THE DISHRAG
Hey, this is…
Okay.
- Let's hang the rest on this.
- It's high.
Nice.
I feel bad now
about having my clothes washed.
Add your clothes to the box
if you have any.
I'll wash them at home
with my washing machine.
No, I'll wash them for you.
Now, it really feels like Kian's B&B.
THE BIZARRE LAUNDRY'S DONE
EXHAUSTED
Hey!
- I'm hungry.
- Me too.
- It's all been digested.
- Right?
Get some rest.
- Yeah.
- I'll cook.
- Rest up and call me later.
- Okay.
- Call us if you need us.
KIAN GOES TO COOK DINNER RIGHT AWAY
Geez.
HE WASHES THE CUTTING BOARD
HE USED TO CUT THE SOAP
"Making a pizza in a frying pan."
Hello?
Hello, we're supposed to check in today.
A NEW GUEST CALLS
Yes, hello.
- Where should we go and by what time?
- What?
By 4:00 p.m., you can come
to the address I'll send you.
Okay.
- Address? Okay.
- How many of you are there?
There are two of us.
- Two people?
- Yes.
All right.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Thank you.
Did you hear that? Two more are coming.
At 4:00 p.m., right?
3:25 A.M.
That's pretty soon.
Then, I should make two more servings.
12 GUESTS IN TOTAL
We should give them welcome drinks later.
Right. Should I make them?
Yesterday, we just mixed
lemon juice with water, but…
They didn't finish them.
I should clean up.
FOUND THE FINISHED THE WELCOME DRINKS
- This.
- How much did you add?
I don't remember how much,
but it was a lot.
But they said it was a bit too sour.
A LOT LIKE YESTERDAY
They couldn't drink it.
How is it?
- This is crazy.
- Really?
TINGLING
I think this might actually kill you.
I'm sweating.
I guess we did make them undrinkable.
What should we add to make them delicious?
- The golden ratio…
- Do we have any honey?
Honey?
Boss, is there honey up there?
Honey? There's oligodang.
But I don't see honey. You want it?
- Yes.
- Here.
OLIGODANG SECURED
Carbonated drinks would be good too.
Fanta?
We should taste them.
CARBONATED DRINK SECURED
JUN-HO JOINS AFTER CHANGING
Taste them?
We're supposed to make the welcome drinks.
ADDING OLIGODANG TO LEMON WATER
Should we add it in?
CURIOUS
It's… not delicious.
It really is not good.
Let's mix in a bit of Fanta.
LEMON WATER, OLIGODANG, SODA
It tastes like
they all made each other worse.
- You can taste all three of them.
- Right.
I think we should go back to square one.
SQUARE ONE?
Let's add a little bit of this to water.
Because lemon juice
is healthy for us.
About 30 drops.
- Two, three.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine.
Okay, I think that's enough.
The color's the same.
I like this.
- This one?
- Yes.
- I like this one too.
- Really?
- Yeah, 30.
- Let's make it 30 drops.
Exactly 30 drops.
THEY FOUND THE GOLDEN RATIO
Yeah, let's do that.
We'll do it when they come.
MEANWHILE, BOSS COOKS DINNER
I should make six pizzas.
TODAY'S DISH
6 KIMCHI CHEESE PIZZAS
SPECIAL TOPPING IS MEAT
- Jun-ho, can you help me cook the meat?
- Sure.
What else do you need help with?
I only need help with the meat.
Got it.
WHILE JUN-HO GRILLS THE MEAT
KIAN PREPS THE TOPPINGS
CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS?
I should make different spice levels.
Extreme, medium, and mild.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
- Right?
- Yeah.
5 CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
8 CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
ADDING 5 MORE
13 CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS SO FAR
More peppers.
ADDING 7 MORE
Gosh, it's spicy.
20 CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS PREPPED
Gosh, my back.
HE MAKES THE DOUGH RIGHT AWAY
It's my first time making pizza.
Geez.
You're even making dough.
Do you know how to make pizza dough?
It's all just flour in the end.
I thought there was a ratio.
- Ratio?
- Yeah.
I have no idea. I'm just going by feel.
They say beating it makes it better.
Become delicious.
You're literally beating it up.
Hand-beaten.
HAND-BEATEN DOUGH
All done.
Aren't you supposed to shape the dough
into a ball and let it rest?
Normally, yes.
But as I punched it, it already fermented.
DOUGH IS READY
AFTER FERMENTING IT WITH PUNCHES
Put oil in the pan.
ADDS MORE OIL
AND ADDS EVEN MORE
This one's big, so…
Why is it so sticky?
All right.
Be careful.
I didn't turn on the stove yet.
Spread it out.
It looks like a hotteokpancake.
Right?
Gosh, this is…
Shouldn't it be thinner?
It should, but…
NO MATTER HOW HARD HE TRIES
IT DOESN'T GET THINNER
Hey, this is… Hold on.
This is not right.
What do I do?
Why won't it spread out?
This is bad.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Why won't it spread out?
FLUSTERED
I'll try to save this.
HE GRABS IT
With the oil, I think it'll work.
AFTER RUBBING OIL ON IT,
HE TRIES TO SPREAD IT OUT AGAIN
Hey, it's spreading out now.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- I see.
- Wide like this.
SECOND PIZZA
This God damn thing.
Man, making pizza is so hard.
Of course.
I guess it does require skill.
I've always only made Korean food.
Nice and wide.
THIRD PIZZA
Make it wide.
Jun-ho, could you take some dough
- and try to make one?
- Sure.
I should try it too.
I think…
Yeah, we should use a rolling pin.
Then, you can toss it.
You're right. That's what I was missing.
I think you made the dough well.
- Not bad, right?
- Yeah.
I think you could toss it
if you stretched it out.
Gently like this.
It's getting wider.
Right?
Yeah.
- Good. It's gotten wider.
- It's gotten big.
Yeah. It gets pretty big.
Yes.
Why does mine
look like a mung bean pancake?
PUTTING TOMATO SAUCE
ON MUNG BEAN PANCAKE?
Gosh, I put in too much oil.
This will be the spiciest one.
Cheongyang chili pepper.
A bunch of it.
A LOT OF CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
SECOND PIZZA
A BUNCH OF CHILI PEPPERS AGAIN?
THIRD ONE HAS A LOT AS WELL
All three ended up as spicy ones.
It'll be all right.
AND A LOT OF OTHER TOPPINGS
BIG
MEANWHILE
JUN-HO CUTS HIS TOPPINGS
INTO BITE-SIZED PIECES
I like adding the chili peppers.
But our Japanese guest
might not be able to eat spicy food.
- That must be a basic one.
- Right, it is.
JUN-HO MAKES A MILD ONE
THE LAST TWO ARE MADE
WITH ONLY KIMCHI AND CHEESE
Adjusting the heat is key.
WAITING UNTIL THEY COOK
Weak enough not to burn it.
I think this is ready.
THEY CHECK IF IT COOKED WELL
Open it.
- It looks good now.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- It doesn't look too bad.
See if the dough's burnt.
Is it burnt or not?
Hey, it's…
It's become pretty crisp. Let's just…
Let's scrape it off.
Then, it'll be all right.
If we scrape it off
until we see the white part…
It's just like brick oven pizza, isn't it?
Brick oven, my foot.
Let's scrape it off.
What? Is it burnt?
What? No.
It's going well.
We can just get rid of this.
- Damn it.
- Is there a problem?
Damn it.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu